I've created over 180 Ninja Creamy
recipes, and this is the one I find
myself coming back to most often. It is
my Shamrock Oreo McFlurry recipe, under
250 calories, over 20 g of protein, and
it tastes just as good as the one from
McDonald's. I might be better. Let me
show you how to make it. In your pint,
you're going to combine high protein
milk, peppermint extract. I did half of
this 1/4 teaspoon vanilla bean paste,
optionally some green food coloring,
sweetener, salt, and zantham gum. And
we'll blend that all together with an
immersion blender. Throw the cover on
and put it in the freezer for at least
16 hours. Once it's completely frozen
through, you can take it out and run it
under hot water for 30 seconds to a
minute and then throw it in your creamy
on the light ice cream setting. Now,
let's talk about the most important part
of the recipe, the Oreos. You can
obviously use whichever Oreos you want.
I use five Oreo thins with the cream
remove. This saves about half the
calories of each cookie, making them 20
calories instead of the usual 35. Of
course, feel free to leave the cream in,
add 10 cookies, do whatever you want.
But if there's one thing that you have
to do, it's make this recipe